<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Question Answering on Alessandro Suglia</title>
    <link>https://alesuglia.github.io/tags/question-answering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Question Answering on Alessandro Suglia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alesuglia.github.io/tags/question-answering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Multi-document Neural Attention for Multiple Answer Prediction</title>
      <link>https://alesuglia.github.io/projects/imnamap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alesuglia.github.io/projects/imnamap/</guid>
      <description>People have information needs of varying complexity, which can be solved by an intelligent agent able to answer questions formulated in a proper way, eventually considering user context and preferences. In a scenario in which the user profile can be considered as a question, intelligent agents able to answer questions can be used to find the most relevant answers for a given user.
In this work we propose a novel model based on Artificial Neural Networks to answer questions with multiple answers by exploiting multiple facts retrieved from a knowledge base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schema-aware Translating Embeddings model</title>
      <link>https://alesuglia.github.io/projects/schema_transe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alesuglia.github.io/projects/schema_transe/</guid>
      <description>We implemented a Torch Deep Learning model able to learn Knowledge Graph embeddings from knowledge base triples. We modified the original negative sampling procedure presented in the paper Translating Embeddings for Modeling Multi-relational Data by incorporating constraints derived from the Ontology schema in order to learn more effective and expressive representations.
https://github.com/aleSuglia/schema-transe</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iterative multi-document neural attention for multiple answer prediction</title>
      <link>https://alesuglia.github.io/publications/imnamap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alesuglia.github.io/publications/imnamap/</guid>
      <description>People have information needs of varying complexity, which can be solved by an intelligent agent able to answer questions formulated in a proper way, eventually considering user context and preferences. In a scenario in which the user profile can be considered as a question, intelligent agents able to answer questions can be used to find the most relevant answers for a given user. In this work we propose a novel model based on Artificial Neural Networks to answer questions with multiple answers by exploiting multiple facts retrieved from a knowledge base.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>